https://technomartrga.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Aenean Cras Tortor
Privacy PolicyWhen Technomart receives information about your session or about you, we may use it for research, regulatory purposes, or to improve our site. In general, on Technomartrga.com, IP addresses (the internet address of a computer) are logged to track a user’s session while the user remains anonymous. This data is analyzed for certain trends and statistics, such as which parts of our site users are visiting and how long they spend there, among other possible uses.
Personal Information – Collection and UseTechnomart is commited to repecting its user’s privacy. In general, you can visit Technomartrga.com without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself.
There are times when we may need information from you, such as your name, mailing address or e-mail address. You will be asked to supply that information voluntarily. Some examples of when we may need information are if you choose to purchase a product or service directly from the Technomartrga.com or to contact us about our website or services. We collect nonpublic personal information from applications or other forms that you submit to us, and from your transactions with us, our affiliates, or others, and from consumer reporting agencies. We will not sell your personal information to or share it with any other company or third party agency, except as permitted by law. We disclose such nonpublic personal information about you only to those employees who have a need to know. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to guard your nonpublic personal information.
Contact us for a complimentary investment portfolio review
Tweets by joseph_parnes
